https://www.fhaonline.biz/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Professional Mortgage Source LLC
TODAY'S RATESPURCHASE ASSISTANTREFINANCE ADVISORDEBT CONSOLIDATORCALCULATORAPPLY NOW
Privacy Policy
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others; and
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency.
We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law.
We may share all the information that we collect, as described above, with our affiliates. By sharing this information, we can better serve your financial needs. If you do not wish for us to share this information with our affiliates you may contact us.
We may disclose the following information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as your name, address, social security number, assets, and income;
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as your account balance, payment history, and parties to transactions;
Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as your creditworthiness and credit history.
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations in order to guard your nonpublic personal information.
QUICK QUOTE
Site Links
Home
About
Glossary
Calculators
Find A Realtor
Local Resources
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Contact
Local (303) 351-5500Toll Free (888) 301-1044Email info@fhaonline.bizAddress 6021 South Syracuse Way Suite 305 Greenwood Village, CO 80111
Connect With Us
Regulated by the Colorado Division of Real Estate, CA CFL#603 H231, Loans made in California will be arranged or made pursuant to the Department of Business Oversight California Finance Lenders Law. NMLS#169609
© 2020 www.fhaonline.biz - Professional Mortgage Source LLC - Login
Mortgage Web Leads by 220 Marketing Partners Login
Have a Question?
Call Today: (303) 351-5500HomeAboutRatesPurchaseRefinanceDebt ConsolidatorReal EstateAsk An AgentLoan OptionsRecommended ProfessionalsApply Now
